mission.com 2017-04-22

# Privacy Policy | Mission

Welcome to mission.com (the " **Site** ").  Mission Product Holdings, Inc. (" **Mission** ") knows that you value your privacy, and we want you to know that it is important to us too. We created this Privacy Notice (" **Privacy Notice** ") to explain the types of information collected through the Service (as defined below), how we will use, disclose and protect this information once it is collected, and how you can opt-out of some of our uses and disclosures of your information. 

BY ACCESSING THE SITE OR USING THE INFORMATION, TOOLS, FEATURES, AND FUNCTIONALITY LOCATED ON THE SITE (COLLECTIVELY WITH THE SITE, THE " **SERVICE** "), YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ AND UNDERSTAND THIS PRIVACY NOTICE. 

We reserve the right to modify, alter or update this Privacy Notice at any time, without prior notice, by posting any such modified, altered or updated version of this Privacy Notice on the Site.  All such modifications, alterations and updates will become effective immediately upon posting.  We encourage you to check this page each time you visit the Site. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE SERVICE AFTER ANY MODIFICATIONS, ALTERATIONS OR UPDATES ARE MADE CONSTITUTES YOUR ACKNOWLEDGEMENT OF SUCH CHANGES. 

## 1\. TERMS OF USE

Please review our [Terms of Use](https://www.mission.com/pages/terms-of-use), which also governs your use of the Service, to understand the terms and conditions under which Mission provides products and services to you.

## 2\. INFORMATION COLLECTED BY MISSION

Whenever you access the Site, make a purchase, or otherwise interact with the Service, Personal Information, Aggregate Information, and/or Service Usage Information may be collected about you or your visit.

## A. PERSONAL INFORMATION

"Personal Information" is information that can be used to identify you as an individual or allow someone to contact you. We may collect Personal Information such as your name, age, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card and other payment information, and demographic information in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, the following:

  * You will be asked to submit Personal Information when you sign up for our e-mail newsletters, register for an account with us, create account recovery credentials, make purchases, enter sweepstakes and contests, complete surveys, contribute reviews and other User Content (as defined in the [Terms of Use](https://www.mission.com/pages/terms-of-use)), engage with a social forum through the Service, or send a comment or question (including through the "Contact Us" feature of the Service).
  * When you make a purchase through or from the Service, we may ask you to provide Personal Information needed to process your purchase or provide the services you request. We also collect information about your purchase, such as the items you bought, the price of the items, the payment method you used and if the product was on sale.  In addition, we may ask you to complete a customer satisfaction survey.  If you choose to do so, you may have the ability to provide (at your option) Personal Information in addition to your comments.
  * If you call us for information about products or your purchase, we may ask you to provide Personal Information so that we can properly respond to your requests and/or process your transactions. 

## B. AGGREGATE INFORMATION

Aggregate Information is information about groups of users or our users as a whole that does not specifically identify any single user, such as, without limitation, age, gender, types of products purchased, frequency of Service visits, Service pages accessed most frequently, search terms entered on the Service, types of Submissions (as defined in the [Terms of Use](https://www.mission.com/pages/terms-of-use)), and the frequency of Submissions.  As an example, the number of people who shopped on the Service during a specific time period is Aggregate Information.  We and our third party service providers may collect Aggregate Information as permitted by applicable law.

## C. SERVICE USAGE INFORMATION<

As you use the Internet, a trail of electronic information is left at each web site you visit. This information, which is sometimes referred to as "clickstream data," along with your IP address, can be collected and stored by a web site's server.  Clickstream data includes, for example and without limitation, which operating system and Web browser software you use to access the Service and their settings, the referring page that linked you to the Service, the pages you visit on the Service, the items you click on during your visit, your purchase information, the next website you visit when you leave the Service, any search terms you have entered on the Service or a referral site, and the type of computer or mobile device you use to access the Service (collectively with your IP address, " **Clickstream Information** ").

In addition, we and our third party service providers acting on our behalf may deploy cookies, local shared objects, tracking pixels and other tracking technologies on the Service to collect additional information about your visits (collectively with the Clickstream Information, " **Service Usage Information** ").

  * **Cookies.** We may use "cookies" to keep, and sometimes track, information about you. Cookies are small data files that are sent to your computer or device from a Web server. Cookies track where you travel on our Service and what you look at and purchase. They may store your Service viewing preferences, the information in your shopping cart, your account username, and/or your logged-in status. Cookies may also enable us to relate your use of the Service over time to other information about you, including your Personal Information, and to customize the Service for you. Most browsers can be set to detect cookies and give you an opportunity to reject them, but refusing cookies may, in some cases, inhibit or preclude your use of the Service or its features.  You may need to consult the help area of your browser application for instructions on disabling cookies.
  * **Tracking Pixels.** Certain third parties who provide services to Mission, or with which the Service integrates, may use tracking pixels. Tracking pixels may be used to help verify your viewing or receipt of a Web page or message. Tracking pixels may enable us to relate your viewing or receipt of a Web page or message to other information about you, including your Personal Information. 

The Site code owned and deployed by Mission recognizes "do not track" signals, which may be adjusted in your Internet browser settings; however, certain third party services with which the Service integrates may or may not recognize "do not track" signals.

**By using the Service, you agree to the use of these tracking technologies.   **

## 3\. HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

Mission or one of its third party service providers may use the information collected from and about you for a variety of purposes, including without limitation:

  * processing and fulfilling your transactions;
  * operating and managing the Service and your account with us;
  * responding to your requests, questions, and concerns;
  * understanding your needs and personalizing the Service to fit your interests and history with us;
  * evaluating Site usage and navigation;
  * developing new features and offerings on the Service to improve the Service;
  * sending you marketing communications, including information about products, services, and sales that we think might interest you;
  * contacting you for market research;
  * conducting and administering surveys; and
  * protecting our rights and property.

To perform the above functions, we may match information collected from you through different means or at different times, including Personal Information, Aggregate Information, and Service Usage Information, and use such information along with information obtained from other sources (including third parties) such as demographic information and updated contact information. We or our third party service providers may also use your information to assess the level of interest in, and use of, the Service, our e-mails and our other messaging campaigns, both on an individual basis and in the aggregate.

## 4\. SHARING YOUR INFORMATION

We may share the information we collect from and about you, including Personal Information, Aggregate Information and/or Service Usage Information, with our affiliates, technical consultants, third party auditors and other third party service providers: (i) who make our Service available, enhance its functionality or provide associated services; (ii) who interact with you in processing your orders and/or delivering content, samples, products, services, gifts and prizes; (iii) who need your information in order to provide services to us (or on our behalf); and/or (iv) for our business purposes.

In addition to the foregoing, we may share and disclose your information when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights or property, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud or respond to a government, judicial or other legal request or order.  Please note that we reserve the right to transfer your information in connection with a corporate change, including a merger, acquisition, reorganization, consolidation, liquidation, sale of assets or similar event.

## 5\. OPT OUT PROCEDURES

We will always give you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving emails and other marketing communications from us.  You may tell us that you do not want to receive such messages by clicking on an opt-out link at the bottom of the e-mails you receive or sending us an email at info@mission.com. 

Mission also gives you the option to remove your personal information from its active database, subject to any applicable laws requiring retention.  If you wish to delete your personal information from our active database, please email us at info@mission.com.  Mission is not responsible for removing information from third-party lists or databases of any kind.  Please understand that it may take us a few days to process any opt-out request and that even if you opt-out of receiving promotional correspondence from us, we may still contact you in connection with your relationship, activities, transactions and communications with us.

## 6\. REVIEWING OR CHANGING YOUR INFORMATION

In order to ensure that the information we maintain is accurate, Mission gives users the ability to change or modify their information previously provided.  You may review, update or modify certain of the Personal Information that is stored in our database by emailing us at info@mission.com, or through your settings under "[My Account](https://www.mission.com/account/login)" on the Service.  If you send Mission a request via email, Mission may ask you to verify your identity and to provide other details before Mission is able to provide you with any information, correct any inaccuracies or delete any information.  Your right to delete your information is subject to our records retention policies.  Mission is not responsible for updating information contained in third-party lists or databases. 

## 7\. DISCUSSIONS AND COMMUNITY TOOLS

Mission may, from time to time, make forums, message boards, news groups and other community tools available to our users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information for other users to view and for Mission to use in accordance with our [Terms of Use](https://www.mission.com/pages/terms-of-use).  Please be considerate and respectful of others while using the community spaces to share your opinions and reviews.

You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your Personal Information in these areas, since anyone - not just Mission - may view and use publicly-posted information.

## 8\. SOCIAL NETWORKING SERVICES

We maintain a presence on several social networking platforms, such as Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest, Instagram and YouTube, and some of their features may be incorporated into the Service.  Through these platforms and features, we receive some Personal Information and some Service Usage Information about you, and this Privacy Notice applies to that information as well. In some cases, information about how you use and interact with the Service will be published via your social networking account in accordance with your social networking account privacy settings. In addition, third party social networking platforms have their own privacy policies which explain how those third parties will use and protect your information.  We encourage you to read those policies to understand how your information is treated by such social networking platforms.

## 9\. THIRD PARTY SITES

The Service may contain links to websites that are not owned, operated or controlled by Mission or our affiliates.  All such links are provided solely as a convenience to you. If you use these links, you will leave the Service.  Mission is not responsible for any content, materials or other information located on or accessible from any other website.  Mission does not endorse, guarantee, or make any representations or warranties regarding any other website, or any content, materials or other information located or accessible from such websites, or the results that you may obtain from using such websites.  If you decide to access any other website linked to or from the Service, you do so entirely at your own risk, and the linked website’s posted privacy policy (not this Privacy Notice) will govern the collection and use of your information on it.  We encourage you to read the privacy statements of each and every website visited after leaving the Service to learn about how your information is treated by others.

## 10\. SECURITY

We have and will maintain security measures we deem reasonable and appropriate to secure your Personal Information against inadvertent or illegal loss, destruction, disclosure or access.  ALThough WE will use various technologies and tools to protect your PERSONAL INFORMATION against loss, destruction, disclosure or access, no method of securing data is foolproof or completely effective, and third parties may unlawfully access or intercept data transmissions, communications or stored data, and may unlawfully use the data. Thus, although WE take reasonable measures to protect your PERSONAL INFORMATION, WE DO not and cannot guarantee that your PERSONAL INFORMATION will remain private or secure.

If you create an account through the Service, you will be asked to provide an email address and password. You are responsible for maintaining the strict confidentiality of your account information and password and for restricting access to such information.  You accept all responsibility for all activities that occur under your account credentials, whether or not you authorized such activity.  Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.  Please notify us promptly at info@mission.com of any unauthorized use of your password or account or any other breach of security.

If we believe that the security of your Personal Information may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you of that development. If a notification is appropriate, we will notify you in accordance with applicable law and governmental guidelines. If we have your e-mail address, you may be notified by e-mail. **You consent to the use of e-mail as a means of such notification. If you prefer to be notified using the U.S. Postal Service in this situation, please send us an email at** **info@mission.com.**

## 11\. PROTECTION FOR CHILDREN

This Site is not intended for users under the age of 18 (or the age of majority in your jurisdiction).  Furthermore, we have no intention of collecting Personal Information from children (i.e., individuals under the age of 13).  Where appropriate, we take reasonable measures to inform children not to submit such information to our Site or in response to advertisements.  If a child has provided us with Personal Information, that child's parent or guardian should contact us at info@mission.com or send us a letter marked "Privacy - Urgent" to the address below.  If we learn that a user under the age of 13 has provided us with Personal Information, other than as permitted by law, we will delete such information from our database. 

## 12\. PRIVACY PRECAUTION WARNING

In accordance with Section 4 of this Privacy Notice, please note that we reserve the right to access, share and/or disclose information collected from or about you as required by courts or administrative agencies and to the extent required to permit us to investigate suspected fraud, harassment or other violations of any law, rule or regulation, the Site rules or policies, or the rights of third parties or to investigate any suspected conduct that Mission deems improper.

## 13\. TERRITORY

You should be aware that the United States and other countries have not harmonized their privacy regulations.  The Service is intended for users who are located in the United States and this Privacy Notice satisfies United States regulations.  To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, Mission does not represent that materials on the Service are appropriate or available for use in other locations, and access to the Service and/or the Site Content (as defined in the [Terms of Use](https://www.mission.com/pages/terms-of-use)) from territories where their content is illegal is prohibited.  Persons who choose to access the Service from other locations do so on their own initiative, and are responsible for compliance with local laws, if and to the extent local laws are applicable.  If you are accessing the Service outside of the United States, you agree to the level of privacy protection set forth in this Privacy Notice.

## 14\. CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

If you are a California resident, you may make a request for information about how we have shared your personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. In response to your written request, we will identify the categories of information shared and will include a list of the third parties and affiliates with which it was shared, along with their names and addresses. Please send us an email at info@mission.com to make such request.

## 15\. CONTACTING US

If you have any questions about this Privacy Notice, the practices of the Service, or your dealings with this Site, you can contact us at info@mission.com.

In addition, our mailing address is:  
MISSION  
60 East 42nd Street, Suite 810  
New York, NY 10165  
866.944.6477

## 16\. SITE POLICIES, MODIFICATION, AND SEVERABILITY

This Privacy Notice, along with our [Terms of Use](https://www.mission.com/pages/terms-of-use) and any other posted policies also govern your use of the Service. We reserve the right to modify, alter or update this Privacy Notice at any time, without prior notice, by posting any such modified, altered or updated version of this Privacy Notice on the Site. All such modifications, alterations and updates will become effective immediately upon posting. We encourage you to check this page each time you visit the Site. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE SERVICE AFTER ANY MODIFICATIONS, ALTERATIONS OR UPDATES ARE MADE CONSTITUTES YOUR ACKNOWLEDGEMENT OF SUCH CHANGES.

If any of provision of this Privacy Notice shall be deemed invalid, void, or for any reason unenforceable, that provision shall be deemed severable and shall not affect the validity or enforceability of any remaining terms or conditions herein.

**_Effective Date:_** January 1st, 2017
